cedexis.com 2018-09-24

# Privacy Policy - Cedexis - RUM-Optimized Global Traffic Management

Last updated: 01/08/2018

This policy is intended to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information received through our website, portal, and other online services that link to this policy (together, the “Website”) and through websites operated by our customers who use our services (“Customer Services”). This policy may be updated from time to time for any reason, at our sole discretion. We will notify you of any significant changes to this policy and changes to the way we use your information by posting the new policy on our website (or as required by law). You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Thank you.

If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please contact us at [privacy@cedexis.com](mailto:privacy@cedexis.com) or write to us at:

**Cedexis Inc.**  
ATTN: Privacy Policy  
421 SW 6th Ave, Suite 700  
Portland, OR 97204 USA

In the EU:

**Cedexis Ltd.**  
ATTN: Privacy Policy  
Unit 407, Metal Box Factory  
30 Great Guildford Street  
London, SE1 0HS

### Applicability

This policy, covering Cedexis, Inc. and its subsidiaries Cedexis Ltd and Cedexis SAS, applies to all visitors and users of our Websites (including users of the services on our Websites (i.e., subscribers to any of our plans). This policy also covers our use of information we collect on behalf of customers through our Customer Services, i.e., visitors on sites operated by customers of our Radar, Openmix, and related services. Cedexis provides Customer Services to our customers that enables them to track users of their websites. Please see the section titled “Cedexis Radar, Openmix, and Impact” below for more information about Customer Services. Cedexis does not control the information practices of our customers and partners that use the Customer Services on their websites. Our customers’ and partners’ websites may have their own privacy policies. We strongly encourage visitors to read those websites’ separate privacy policies to learn about their information practices.

### Website Visitors

Cedexis collects information automatically about visits to our Websites, including portals for customer who use our services (“Portals”). Such information may include, for example, the browser used, referring site, and the time and date of each web request. We collect this information to understand how visitors use our Websites. We also collect traffic data, like IP addresses and cookie data and other tracking information as described in our [Cookie Policy](http://cedexis.wpengine.com/cookie-policy/). We also collect information you provide to us, such as your name, title, company, email address and phone number, when you contact us using the contact information or forms included on our Websites.

Other third parties who provide us with services may also collect information described above about your online activities over time and across different Web sites when you visit our Websites.

### Portal Visitors

Information, including username, name, e-mail address, and phone number, is collected from customer employees that are Portal users. We collect information, including a password, needed to identify a Portal user and verify their authorization for the Portal. If you are making payments for certain services, we also collect certain financial account information including credit card data, billing address and billing contact information for users making payments through the Portal. Portal users in the same customer account have access to each other’s email addresses and related information.

### Cookies

A “cookie” is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our Websites. Cedexis’ Website visitors have choices related to cookies and tracking technologies as described in our [Cookie Policy](http://cedexis.wpengine.com/cookie-policy/).

Cookies may also be used by Cedexis and our customers and partners on their websites in connection with our Customer Services. Use of cookies on our customers’ and partners’ websites are covered by their privacy policies. We provide choices related to Cedexis Radar and Impact measurement activity, including as collected through cookies, as described in the Choices section below.

### Cedexis Radar, Openmix, and Impact

Cedexis Radar, Openmix, and Impact are Customer Services provided by Cedexis to help our customers and partners measure and improve Internet user experience and performance of their websites and online services along with other Customer Services. Cedexis collects and processes personal information relating to its Customer Services solely on behalf of our customers in accordance with our agreements with those customers and partners. As part of the operation of our Customer Services, these services collect information, such as the user’s IP address, time of visit, and the browser’s User-Agent, to inform network routing choices and other service decisions. Our customers and partners receive this data and may define additional types of information, including personal information of their users, that may be collected through the Customer Services. The Customer Services may use our customers’ cookies to collect this information. We may also use our own cookies to provide these services. Information about your choices regarding our measurement activities, including through cookies, used in Customer Services is described in the Choices section below.

### Protection of Personally Identifying Information

Cedexis undertakes reasonable security measures to protect data to guard against unauthorized access to personal data. If you use our Portal, you are responsible for safeguarding your username and password. For Customer Services, Cedexis’ security practices are governed by its agreements with its customers and partners.

If you learn of a security issue with our Websites or our Customer Services, please contact us at support@cedexis.com.

### Data Retention and Disaster Recovery

We take reasonable efforts to backup data and distribute it among our geographically dispersed data centers in case of catastrophic failure. Integrity of these backups and the procedures for recovering from catastrophic failure are verified on a regular basis.

Cedexis Openmix and Cedexis Radar logs are typically kept for at least 13 months after use of the service unless otherwise agreed to with our customers and partners. Upon Portal account termination, information is typically retained for at least one year from the time of termination unless otherwise agreed to with our customers and partners.

### Sharing with Third Parties

Cedexis may share personally identifying information with your consent. Cedexis may also share information on an aggregate basis, for example through group-level usage reports.

If you have provided us with information as an employee of a customer, we may share your information with that customer.

We may share some or all of your information with our current or future affiliates, parent companies, subsidiaries, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this policy. We may also share your information in connection with or during a merger, financing, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving the sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets to another company.

Personal information may be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies subject to warrants, subpoenas, or other governmental orders or in the case of an emergency or to protect the rights and property of Cedexis, our agents, customers, and others.

Cedexis utilizes third party data processors in order to provide some functionality. We use infrastructure services for hosting of our platform and data processing, payment processors for billing, and authentication for security.

Third parties engaged by Cedexis to process personal data and any of our affiliates receiving personal data must: (i) comply with the Privacy Shield principles or another mechanism permitted by the applicable EU & Swiss data protection law(s) for transfers and processing of personal data; (ii) or agree to provide adequate protections for the personal data that are no less protective than those set out in this Policy.

Cedexis has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives and subsequently transfers to a third party. Cedexis remains potentially liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if its agent processes such personal data in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

### Choices

If you have an account in connection with our Customer Services, you can use the Cedexis Portal to review and change the personally identifying information stored by Cedexis. If you change your mind about the use of information volunteered by you or would like access to your information, please send us a request to [privacy@cedexis.com](mailto:privacy@cedexis.com) to ask about access to your information or having your information removed or corrected. If you are an end user of our customers’ and partners’ websites that use our Customer Services, please contact those customers or partners to request access to, changes to, or deletion of your information, and we will act at their direction.

If desired, users can opt-out of Cedexis Radar or Impact measurement activity by enabling the Do Not Track configuration settings offered by major browsers. If Do Not Track is enabled in these browsers, Radar and Impact will not collect analytics data nor any identifiable information about the user to be used as part of any aggregated performance measurements. While we make efforts to respond to major web browser signals as described above, there are many ways through which web browser signals and other similar mechanisms can indicate your choice to disable tracking, and we may not be aware of or honor every web browser setting or every mechanism.

When you visit our Websites, we and others give you choices described in our [Cookie Policy](http://cedexis.wpengine.com/cookie-policy/) about use of mechanisms for tracking, including tracking of your online activities over time and across different websites and online services by third parties. While we and others give you choices described in the [Cookie Policy](http://cedexis.wpengine.com/cookie-policy/), there are many ways through which web browser signals and other similar mechanisms can indicate your choice to disable tracking, and we may not be aware of or honor every mechanism.

Our marketing emails tell you how to “opt-out” of receiving further marketing emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails include emails about your accounts and our business dealings with you.

### Privacy Shield

Cedexis complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and under the jurisdiction of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Cedexis has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

Cedexis’s participation in the Privacy Shield applies to all personal data that is subject to our Privacy Policy and is received from the European Union and European Economic Area. We will comply with the Privacy Shield Principles in respect of such personal data.

In compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, Cedexis commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Cedexis using the information provided above.

Cedexis complies with the U.S.-Swiss Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and under the jurisdiction of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland. Cedexis has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

Cedexis’s participation in the Privacy Shield applies to all personal data that is subject to our Privacy Policy and is received from Switzerland. We will comply with the Privacy Shield Principles in respect of such personal data.

In compliance with the U.S.-Swiss Privacy Shield Principles, Cedexis commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Cedexis using the information provided above.

Cedexis has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles and U.S.-Swiss Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism free of charge to you and operated by ICDR/AAA. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [http://info.adr.org/safeharbor](http://info.adr.org/safeharbor) for more information and to file a complaint. A binding arbitration option will also be made available to you in order to address residual complaints not resolved by any other means.
